hidemyipaddress.org 2012-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Hide My IP address - Browse anonymously

### Like & Tweet Hide My IP

### Hide My IP Address e-News

Join to us (

#### Hide My IP Address

) with your email account, and get **fresh proxy list** every day into your mailbox for **FREE**. 

### About you

### Current users hidding IP

### Why us?

Hide My IP address service is free web-based proxy browser, which helps users to browse totaly anonymously. We offer you also unlimited access to popular websites such as Youtube, Myspace or Facebook. We garantee you, that the service is totaly anonymously!. 

## _Welcome_ to **Hide My IP** Address - **FREE** Web Proxy

### Hide My IP Address is 100% PURE and FREE! Try it now!

##  Privacy Policy

Our service may collect information about you during your visit. This document describes the information we collect and how it is used.

**Server Access Logs**

Our server logs all requests. The data recorded includes information provided by your browser (user agent and referring page) as well as the requested URI, the time and date and your IP address. The data recorded in these logs may be used for detecting and preventing abuse. We may also collate this data for statistical purposes.

**Service Logs**

The service provided on this website allows access to external, third-party websites. We may record your IP address and the websites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes.

**Cookies**

Our website stores a cookie on your computer, if allowed by your browser's privacy settings [*](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/privacy.html#browser-settings). The cookie used by our service uniquely identifies you to the server and allows our website to remember your preferences.

We may also use third-party advertising partners on our website. Advertisers may send you cookies or use web beacons. We have no control over cookies, web beacons or the information collected by our advertisers. Consult the third-party advertiser's privacy policy for more information on their practices.

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the websites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party website. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option.

* For more information on configuring your browser, see [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1) or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites.

You can **[hide ip](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/) address**, unblock popular social networking sites such as [MySpace](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/Oi8vd3d3Lk1/5U3BhY2UuY2/9t/b61/), [Bebo](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/Oi8vd3d3Lm/JlYm8uY29t/b61/), [Facebook](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/Oi8vd3d3LmZh/Y2Vib29rLmNv/bQ_3D_3D/b61/), [YouTube](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/Oi8vd3d/3LnlvdX/R1YmUuY/29tLw_3/D_3D/b61/), [Orkut](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/czovL3d3dy5nb/29nbGUuY29tL2/FjY291bnRzL1N/lcnZpY2VMb2dp/bj9zZXJ2aWNlP/W9ya3V0JmhsPW/VuLVVTJnJtPWZ/hbHNlJmNvbnRp/bnVlPWh0dHAlM/0ElMkYlMkZ3d3/cub3JrdXQuY29/tJTJGUmVkaXJM/b2dpbi5hc3B4J/TNGbXNnJTNEMC/UyNnBhZ2UlM0R/odHRwJTI1M0El/MjUyRiUyNTJGd/3d3Lm9ya3V0Lm/NvbSUyNTJGSG9/tZS5hc3B4JmNk/PVVTJnBhc3Npd/mU9dHJ1ZSZza2/lwdnBhZ2U9dHJ/1ZSZzZW5kdmVt/YWlsPWZhbHNl/b61/), [Friendster](http://www.hidemyipaddress.org/browse.php/Oi8vd3d3Lm/ZyaWVuZHN0/ZXIuY29tLw/_3D_3D/b61/), make uncensored browsing and surf totaly secured on the Internet from home, school, job or cafe - **from everywhere**.

With HideMyIPaddress.org proxy you will get completely insurance from viruses, bots and other unwanted stuff!

The ability to hide your IP address increases your privacy on the Internet. Other approaches to improving Internet privacy and security also exist and complement each other. Managing Web browser cookies, using encryption when sending personal information, running a firewall and other techniques all contribute toward a greater feeling of **safety** and **security** when going online.

| If you like service, help us to be better with small donation via PayPal.  
---|---
